what about radioactive elements mmm
touchy I haven't tried any of that
because I don't like playing with
radioactive elements I will tell you
this I don't know if I've said it before
in a lecture or not but radioactivity
everything conductivity radioactivity
magnetism comes down to crystal and
geometrical structure nikola tesla
theorized that radioactivity was a
manifestation of cosmic rays interacting
with with what's a uranium a radioactive
rock was a radiation was the result of
cosmic rays interacting with it if we
could shield it properly the radiation
would go away so a friend of his didn't
agree with this at all and wanted to
prove him wrong about twenty years later
he had the opportunity and they were
drilling one of the deepest deepest
holes on the entire planet I think they
went down 18,000 feet and this gentleman
was involved with it he wanted to prove
Tesla wrong and so he took a radioactive
powerful radioactive sample and strapped
a counter probe to it and lowered it
down into this hole when he got down to
about 16,000 feet and the meter that
they've got up there it's just buzzing
because it's right next to the sample it
get done 16,000 feet and it turns off
what that shows is that the crystalline
structure of the metal is is interacting
with the Rays that are hitting the
planet of when it got down to about
16,000 feet it was no longer interacting
with those rays anymore and there wasn't
a matter of a court getting disconnected
no no when they pulled it back up hit
about actually they got it back up and
it stopped buzzing and it took about two
hours for that sample to start
generating radiation again so it has
everything to do with energy coming in
which actually tells us something very
interesting if we can create I mean
that's a radio that's that's energy
coming out of that that sample if we can
find the proper crystal of June
while structure my quenelle is actually
working on this and in a little bit
different way we can actually you know
we could actually create a place or a
substance with the proper crystalline
structure that take who make all the
energy we could ever want from cosmic
radiation cosmic rays okay
the day-night solar cell is an example
of this so just something to do
something to experiment with so that's
why we can remediate a nuclear radiation
with proper grounds gas not the not the
weak stuff but the good stuff it just it
changes the entire crystalline structure
of the material so it is no longer
responding to the cosmic rays we did an
experiment with some coal electricity
stuff that you know we hooked up a cold
electricity generator to a caduceus wand
and we ran it over some powerful alpha
radiation samples and it would they
completely uh all the radiation went
away for about thirty minutes so and
then it slowly came back so there's
different ways to do it radiation is not
the boogeyman that that the governments
and the universities and hydro people of
the world would like us to believe it is
I mean it's dangerous don't get me wrong
but you can get rid of it in many
different ways but that's another story
entirely I'm sorry I digress a lot
let's summarize I've got seven minutes
left on my battery I've got more on my
tape it in this setting since it'll be
hard to get back into the same let's go
ahead and wrap it up kind of describing
the process and and the mechanism and
give us a take-home lesson what we are
doing is we are utilizing a hydrogen
electrolysis cell just like this well
wet cell there's a dry cell but same
principle we're using a hydrogen
electrolysis cell we are seeding it with
elements we use the the hydrogen and
oxygen that comes off for whatever
purposes
the power or heat generation and our
by-product that's going to collect in
the bottom as the more we run is
elements that we state it with and what
we are looking at is the ability to take
hydrogen and oxygen imprint a template
on them and order the energy into
physical reality literally electricity
becoming becoming physical reality and
if and if we want to you know debate
numbers I'll just throw this out there
in one cubic centimeter of the vacuum
there exists enough energy to power the
United States for an entire year so if
we are working with the implosion and
the and the changes of hydrogen and
oxygen that we experience and hydrolysis
cell how much energy are we actually
playing with from the vacuum so this is
basically view with basically an
elemental copy machine
elemental copy machine is a good way to
put it powered by the motors of the
universe so any final questions from the
audience before we never I'm not
igniting any of this no you're still
storing it for a future use well that's
but that's over here in this system I
can I have just bled this off into the
when you see salt water would you say
like salt sea water or just sodium
chloride that we I was able salt thank
you for asking that I would not
recommend using straight salt water I
would only use seawater I'm gonna build
an entirely different machine and to use
seawater it because I don't want to run
I don't want to mess this one up I like
playing with it further without all my
others
only seawater saltwater Brian from the
oil wells the Great Salt Lake water
Great Salt Lake is a fantastic source of
very interesting elements never never
straight saltwater saltwater you're
going to pour up a huge amount of
chlorine gas and really bad stuff so
thank you for bringing that out ok any
other final comments questions so the
hydrogen and oxygen is also a chemical
do the calculations you you mentioned
how much hydrogen you just he just said
right not if you do back on the back of
your hand you can do the calculations
oxygen oxygen that you have yeah I
wasn't named that promise i absolutely
forgot about that it's about 16 times
yeah yeah that was the thing was cameras
so is it possible that the electrolysis
of the water is not necessarily the
crucial ingredient but that the it sets
a context of copying that includes
copying the water the the hydrogen and
oxygen and whatever other elements are
in the water
[Music]
forgive me I forgotten his name he was
responsible for their the Nuclear
Regulatory Agency in Japan of here and
their laboratory he got talked into
doing this
and so we ran the test took iron
electrodes just straight iron electrodes
999 fewer and did exactly what you
measured the amount of hydrogen and
oxygen and when he got far more than we
suppose but then they spent their four
pages of the article trying to say what
was happening at the molecular level
when they got through there was no
conclusion okay this is one of three or
four different possible ways but they
all right so we're almost out of time
but I'd like to I'd like to finish that
trailer bring back here well quite water
separates into steam at 1,800 to one
volume okay so one liter of water will
create 1,800 liters of steam good Browns
gas will and then so we use that as a
rule of thumb and that's that's where
these figures come from what we would
expect to find but good Browns gas can
produce much much more volume than just
the 1802 one so that's what we're saying
where is that coming from I completely
forgot about that word exactly so this
device as was mentioned earlier this
device produces about twenty liters of
gas an hour and so it's not a huge
volume but over time twenty of these
we've got an hour for an eight hour
Sunday day definitely enough gas to cook
meals and maybe even heat a house if
you're going to use it to heat my shelf
this summer or this winter so there are
many many facets of this and many
applications and and I encourage
everybody to jump in feet first and
experiment with it and see where it goes
because as we
from Al and other people have talked
this week and there are other
experiments this is being proved out
over and over again now it's time to
actually focus on it and see where we
can take it because water is the future
of this planet we don't find ways to
more effectively utilize our water you
know we're not that we're not going to
make it so thank you very much for all
your time and everything thanks for
being here but radioactivity everything
conductivity radioactivity magnetism
comes down to crystal and geometrical
structure nikola tesla theorized that
radioactivity was a manifestation of
cosmic rays interacting with with what's
a uranium a radioactive rock was a
radiation was the result of cosmic rays
interacting with deepest holes on the
entire planet I think they went down
18,000 feet and this gentleman was
involved with it he wanted to prove
Tesla wrong and so he took a radioactive
powerful radioactive sample and strapped
a what about radioactive elements mmm
radioactive elements are touchy I
haven't tried any of that because I
don't like playing with radioactive
elements yeah I will tell you this I
don't know if I've said it before in a
lecture or not than if we could shield
it properly the radiation would go away
so a friend of his didn't agree with
this at all and wanted to prove him
wrong about 20 years later he had the
opportunity and they were drilling one
of the deepest